<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Texts>
  <Block>
    <ID>CHAT_A_BTN_01</ID>
    <Text>∈</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>eve002_01</ID>
    <Text>I am the captain of Unit 1. This is Ensign Alan Aylward.
It was suddenly organized as a combat unit, but that's all.
Since expectations are high, let's do our best.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>eve003_01</ID>
    <Text>I'm Corporal Hoare Blanchett, and I'm the unit's operator.
We collect, analyze, and communicate information so that you can concentrate on the battle.
I will do it.  thank you.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>eve004_01</ID>
    <Text>This is Sergeant Dennis Barrow.
I wonder if he will be the only one with actual combat experience in this unit.  Best regards from now!
Eh, especially the cute girls!</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>eve005_01</ID>
    <Text>Hahaha… Dennis, I rely on you for so many things.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>eve005b_01</ID>
    <Text>Jeez…. By all means, such a mysterious force...
I guess I'm being transferred...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>eve005b_02</ID>
    <Text>I'm Warrant Officer Lil Somers from Augusta.
Although he has no actual combat experience, he is quite skilled at piloting MS.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>eve005b_03</ID>
    <Text>Well, I think they'll be poached from the elite forces soon.
Until then, thank you!</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>eve006_01</ID>
    <Text>Augusta means test pilot...
That seems promising. Thank you for your support both in public and private life.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>eve007_01</ID>
    <Text>Hmm! I have no intention of getting along with you!
nice to meet you!</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>eve008_01</ID>
    <Text>Hehehe...I was relieved to see so many fun people.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>eve009_01</ID>
    <Text>Well, there are many people, including myself, who have no actual combat experience.
They are members with high potential, so as long as they gain experience,
We should be able to make a good team.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>eve009_02</ID>
    <Text>First of all, we will complete this mission perfectly and
I'll prove to you that I'm a right staff!</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>aln161_01</ID>
    <Text>Now, everyone, get ready to sortie!</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>eve703_01</ID>
    <Text>Roger that!</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>test</ID>
    <Text>１２３４５６７８９０１２３４５６７８９０１２３４５６７８９０
１２３４５６７８９０１２３４５６７８９０１２３４５６７８９０
１２３４５６７８９０１２３４５６７８９０１２３４５６７８９</Text>
  </Block>
</Texts>