<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Texts>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME01</ID>
    <Text>Universal Century 0079. September 26th.


To me, who passed the MS pilot aptitude test,


With the notice of early graduation from the military academy,


Orders were given for assignment to newly established units.



After Zeon's Earth descent operation,


The war situation had been in a stalemate for half a year,


Right now, he was about to start moving.



And then, the fateful October 6th.


I am a member of the 1st platoon of the wide-area special response MS unit.


As a platoon leader of the so-called "SRT-Unit 1",


He was assigned his first actual combat mission,


I met the friends I will be fighting with from now on...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME02</ID>
    <Text>The Earth Federation Forces are



The event in Odessa is scheduled to take place soon.



Warsaw was used as a rallying point for the big counteroffensive operation.



We have begun moving troops from each base.






On the same day, we celebrated our first match with a victory,



A new order has come from the upper management.






It ended a months-long stalemate and



It was a sign that the Federation was about to launch a counter-offensive operation.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME03</ID>
    <Text>The federal army's major counter-offensive operation.


Preparations for "Operation Odessa" are complete.



In order to secure victory,


To avoid concentration of Zeon forces, the final attack target is


I have to hide it until the very last moment.



For that purpose, we have many diversionary troops.


It will be rolled out in various places,


General Reville sends a tiger cub MS unit to this.


I decided to invest in it.



While MS units that had reached a certain level of proficiency were selected,


He had experienced combat twice and achieved considerable results.


A muster order has been given to our troops...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME04</ID>
    <Text>The units participating in the Federal Army's big counteroffensive operation are:

We reached Warsaw, our rallying point.


Preparations for Operation Odessa

Things are steadily coming together.


In order to secure victory,

Avoid concentration of Zeon forces,

The final attack target is

I have to hide it until the very last moment.


For that purpose, we have many diversionary troops.

It will be rolled out in various places,

General Reville sends a tiger cub MS unit to this.

I decided to invest in it.


While MS units that had reached a certain level of proficiency were selected,

Experienced two actual battles,

For our troops, who had achieved considerable success,

I received a summons order...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME05</ID>
    <Text>November 7th.


At last, "Operation Odessa" began.



A large force of federal troops gathered in Warsaw.


Targeting the mineral resource extraction base in Odessa


Start marching.


Zeon, on the other hand, is a member of the European Suppression Force.


Under the command of Major General Yuri Kelane,


Attempts were made to resist by reducing the defensive line.


The federal army was at a stalemate,


The battle was temporarily at a stalemate.



Meanwhile, we were on a mission to protect the rear troops.


It was decided that I would arrive...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME06</ID>
    <Text>The Zeon troops defending Odessa were


As soon as they saw that they were outnumbered, they quickly retreated and tried to escape.


Many of his defeated troops


They fled to Africa and the Far East.



Although both armies suffered heavy losses,


The Battle of Odessa ended with a victory for the Federal Army.


The military balance on the ground is


It tilted heavily toward the Federation.



We will replace the exhausted main force,


I was assigned to patrol the surrounding area.



We are also quite exhausted...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME07</ID>
    <Text>The Zeon troops defending Odessa were


As soon as they saw that they were outnumbered, they quickly retreated and tried to escape.


Many of his defeated troops


They fled to Africa and the Far East.





Although both armies suffered heavy losses,


The Battle of Odessa ended with a victory for the Federal Army.


The military balance on the ground is


It tilted heavily toward the Federation.





We faced a group of enemies escaping to the Far East.


It was decided that a surprise attack would be carried out...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME08</ID>
    <Text>The Zeon European Suppression Force has lost its chain of command.


At the height of confusion,


In various places, to areas where the front line is still maintained.


One after another, the troops fled.


Finally, a small number of MS units were recognized for their abilities.


A guerrilla attack on the routed troops and a mop-up battle


This became his main mission.



Of course, our troops are no exception.


The order was given to sortie for a mop-up battle. 　


Chase and annihilate the fleeing enemies.


I don't feel like it, but in order not to spread the flames of war needlessly,


It had to be done...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME09</ID>
    <Text>By the Far East Asia Army, Kojima Battalion,


To Lhasa base, Zeon's base


A siege has begun.


After completing Operation Odessa, we will deploy to the city area.


Of the mass-produced Guntank bombardment unit,


He was assigned to fill in the gaps in security.


The Kojima Battalion has been around since the beginning of the Federal Army.


Because it is a unit that actually operated MS,


Even if we can just exchange information,


It can be said to be a big gain for us.


...And so on, we at this time...

Swallowed by Odessa's victory and its mood,

Maybe I was underestimating the fight a little...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME10</ID>
    <Text>November 18th.

It has now become a battlefield myth.

The amphibious assault ship ``White Base'' belongs to the Federation Forces.

Arrived at Belfast base.



On November 21st, the base was attacked by Zeon marine forces.

Although the base garrison suffered a devastating blow,

Due to the activities of the MS unit belonging to White Base,

she fought it off.



White Base is the headquarters of the Earth Federation Forces.

Departing for Jaburo, Belfast base,

They were busy reinforcing the base garrison.



But she got the information

The movement of Zeon's ground forces has been confirmed.

We are in a different form with White Base,

It was decided that he would be in charge of defending the Belfast base...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME11</ID>
    <Text>We were removed from the joint operation with Kojima Battalion.

After the move, the Lhasa base fell.


Due to the appearance of new enemy weapons, friendly forces also

It seems like a lot of damage has been done, but now it's even worse.

The defeated Zeon forces were left with nowhere to go.



Unfortunately, the commander of the 08th platoon

Apparently, he went missing during the process...


I wanted to talk to him slowly someday.


I really wish he was alive...



Even so,

In this case, an MS unit with actual combat experience

I was once again reminded of how rare it is within the Federation Forces.


As for MS development and production,

Pilot training doesn't seem to be going well...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME12</ID>
    <Text>End of November.


In Jaburo, South America, where the Federal Forces General Headquarters is located.

we were summoned.


In Jaburo, it was rebuilt by the Vinson plan.

Starfleet and MS, which has been mass-produced,

The launch was coming soon.

Gather troops who are already operating MS in actual combat,

In response to voices from the field who wanted to hear helpful opinions,

It seems that our troops have been contacted as well.

The battles we have fought so far will also be felt by the upper management.

That it was properly evaluated

I was happy to be able to confirm this.


However, at the same time,

Zeon's largest base on earth,

From California Base,

A large force to capture Jaburo is fighting for a comeback.

It was taking off...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME13</ID>
    <Text>November 30th.


Zeon's descent strategy against Jaburo is

It was reaching a climax.



Against the Federation, which responds with overwhelming numbers,

Zeon takes on the challenge with determination to the death.

At great cost, some MS

They had succeeded in infiltrating inside Jaburo.



If you take the time, you can wipe these out.

It was easy, but

If damage is caused to the rebuilt fleet,

The counterattack into space after this will be significantly delayed.

You will be forced to do so.



Quickly destroy all enemy MS

The federal army that must be eliminated is

I could tell that I was in a predicament...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME14</ID>
    <Text>December 2.


Starfleet launched from Jaburo.


From now on, the main battlefield of the battle is


It will move to space.



However, the battle on the ground is not over yet.


Due to the failure of the Jaburo landing operation,


The Zeon ground forces suffered a fatal loss of strength.


The Federal Forces saw this as an opportunity, and their two major bases,


For the California base and the African front,


Preparations for a large-scale mopping-up operation begin.



Meanwhile, for some reason, our troops...


An order has been given to test the new MS...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME15</ID>
    <Text>As of December,

Zeon's ground forces had already virtually collapsed.


Commanders from all over the world quickly escape into space,

Soldiers on the front lines lost their chain of command.

I ended up being left behind.


Those who believe in the coming counterattack and go into hiding as soon as possible.


Trying to return to my home in space,

A wanderer looking for a way out to one of the few space bases.


Barely supporting the front lines,

A person attempting to escape to the African continent.


Zeon ground forces continue to wander around the world...


On the other hand, the Federation, in order to move its main battlefield to space,

Launching the rebuilt space fleet from Jaburo,

The momentum was increasing further.


Meanwhile, a new order has been given to our unit...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME16</ID>
    <Text>As of December,


Zeon's ground forces had already virtually collapsed.



Commanders from all over the world quickly escape into space,


Soldiers on the front lines lost their chain of command.


I ended up being left behind.



Those who believe in the coming counterattack and go into hiding as soon as possible.



Trying to return to my home in space,


A wanderer looking for a way out to one of the few space bases.



Barely supporting the front lines,


A person attempting to escape to the African continent.



Zeon ground forces continue to wander around the world...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME17</ID>
    <Text>The worst doubt that crossed my mind during the last battle was

Were they really Zeon?

I'm saying that….

If they hadn't attacked Midea,

I was convinced it was Zeon, but...

The Zeon troops must be in need of supplies and a way to escape.

For attacking Midea without asking,

I couldn't think of a convincing reason...


Originally, we were the ones who established our unit in a somewhat forced manner.

General Reville, but also that general.

Now it has gone up into space...


Caught up in factional conflicts among the military's upper echelons,

There are many cases of murders that are not made public.

However, the truth is that this truth will never be revealed.

As a soldier and a captain, I knew this.


However, everyone in the unit

I was angry at myself for putting myself at risk for no reason.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME18</ID>
    <Text>December 5th.


The African clean-up operation has finally begun.


Federal forces are heading to the California base in North America.


A mopping-up operation also started at the same time.


With the completion of these two large-scale operations,


The battle on Earth was about to end.



Our troops are


He was assigned to serve as a rear unit in the African clean-up operation.


In Odessa, the beachhead,


I will protect the troops that are gathering and send them to the front line...


The first stage of the final battle is


The content was surprisingly simple...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME19</ID>
    <Text>December 5th.


The Federation Forces called it a Zeon mop-up operation.

Africa and North America California based

A mopping-up operation has begun against the two major bases.


With the completion of these two mop-up operations,

The Zeon mopping up operation on Earth is

It will come to an end once.



Our unit is in charge of capturing the California base.

They were kept at the rear as a reserve force.



A week has passed since the start of the operation,

Troops on the move as additional strength,

She disappeared near Seattle.


We are

In order to investigate the cause,

I decided to go scout the ruins of Seattle...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME20</ID>
    <Text>The African clean-up operation started on December 5th.

They were having trouble facing Zeon's resistance, which was greater than expected.


Lieutenant Colonel Rommel, Major Roy Grinwood, etc.

Zeon's famous aces,

that it was functioning effectively;

They sent in an army of amateurs based on quantity alone.

The federation's upper echelons are naive,

I would have to say that was the biggest factor...


Moreover, all over Africa

Underground bases using abandoned mines are troublesome;

Discovering and conquering them was extremely difficult.


We are presumed to be one of the enemy's bases.

Alone from Midea to the mining base in the Ahaggar Mountains.

It was decided to carry out a landing assault operation.


It's a very dangerous mission, but

If I can't accomplish it somehow...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_ME21</ID>
    <Text>December 15th.

Finally, the California base capture team

The invasion was extending its reach to the vicinity of the base.

Finally, it's time for checkmate.



California Base was originally a base for the Federal Army.

The vast grounds are home to four armies: land, sea, air, and space.

It is a base with multiple residences.

moreover,

It even has a technical research center and factory for weapons development.

Retaking this base is

For the Federation, this was something to be desired.



We headed to the area that corresponds to the air base.

He was assigned to lead the invasion.



It's a very dangerous mission, but

If I can't accomplish it somehow...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME01_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Seattle</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME02_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Desert</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME03_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Africa</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME04_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Valley</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME05_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Near Odessa</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME06_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Near Odessa</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME07_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Desert</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME08_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Snow field</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME09_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Lhasa Base</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME10_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Belfast Base</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME11_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Valley, Area 526</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME12_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Jaburo, surface</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME13_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Jaburo, underground</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME14_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Valley</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME15_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Snow field</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME16_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Ghobi Desert</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME17_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Arctic Base</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME18_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Near Odessa</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME19_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Seattle</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME20_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Africa Mining Base</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_ME21_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>California Base</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ01</ID>
    <Text>Universal Century 0079.

After the British Campaign and the Loum Campaign,

Zeon failed in his plan to force the Federation to surrender unconditionally.

Started direct invasion of the ground.

My best friend Klaus and I participated in the second landing operation.

As an auxiliary member of the 2nd Ground Mobile Division,

landed on the ground.


The invasion operation was carried out in a blitzkrieg manner,

The situation ended with the securing of major resource mining areas and military bases.

During that time, I served as reinforcements.

He was appointed as the platoon leader of the MS platoon that was brought down to the ground.

Removed from the direct control of the various military forces,

As a handyman, he is sent to skirmishes all over the place.


A breakthrough in the war, which had been at a stalemate for a long time.

When suspicious movements of the federal army began to be detected,

To my worn-out "Brauer Platoon",

With new operators as supplementary personnel

A veteran MS pilot has been assigned.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ02</ID>
    <Text>centered on Europe

Starting with the activation of suspicious troop movements by the Federal Army,

At the end of October, scattered fighting began in various areas.

It was clear that these were some kind of diversion.


The information about the Federation Forces MS we encountered last time is

Due to the above decision, it was never made public.

As before, many Zeon soldiers,

A powerful latest weapon called MS

I believed that only our army possessed it.


If you ask me,

A vague sense of anxiety caused by rumors spreading...

And, thinking about the confusion that would arise if I encountered it,

Obtaining views from upper management in a formal manner

I think I should announce it...


Well, after all,

For those who stand on top, the atmosphere of the battlefield etc.

I guess I can't feel it...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ03</ID>
    <Text>It was carried out after nine months of silence.

Due to the Federation Forces' major counter-offensive, Zeon

We have lost our largest mineral resource mining base.

Major Ma Qube quickly abandoned Odessa,

He escapes from the earth.

The amount of resources sent from here to the home country is

It is said that it can easily withstand 10 years of war,

The actual battle is

Soldiers on the front lines, including us...

Honestly, there's no way I could survive such a long battle.

That was the reality.

With the defeat of Odessa,

What had the greatest influence on future battles was

It was not a loss of a resource extraction base, but a defense.

The European Suppression Force suffered severe damage.

The chain of command was in complete confusion.

The front line troops began to flee on their own,

The battles started to be disorganized,

The battle on the ground becomes a quagmire,

I could feel it too...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ04</ID>
    <Text>As an independent guerrilla force, we


As a unit that acts based on its own judgment


We have started our activities.




The defeat of the European Domination Army continued, and many units


Escape to space, to Africa and the Far East


He was making a withdrawal move.




Let as many friendly forces escape safely as possible,


In order to rebuild the front,


We thoroughly collect information,


We plan to move to different areas where support is needed.


I had decided.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ05</ID>
    <Text>As an independent guerrilla force, we


As a unit that acts based on its own judgment


We have started our activities.




The defeat of the European Domination Army continued, and many units


Escape to space, to Africa and the Far East


He was making a withdrawal move.




Let as many friendly forces escape safely as possible,


In order to rebuild the front,


We thoroughly collect information,


We plan to move to different areas where support is needed.


I had decided.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ06</ID>
    <Text>One of the largest bases of the Zeon Ground Suppression Force.

California base.



this is,

Centered around the bases of the three military forces, land, sea, and air.

A space base equipped with a large launch catapult,

It even has a weapons development factory on its premises.

It's a large complex.



This base was originally a base for the Federal Army.

During the second Earth landing operation, Zeon

succeeded in capturing it with almost no damage.

It was being repurposed.



We suffered a crushing defeat in Europe,

To go on the offensive against the Federation again

Whether we can do it or not depends on the survival of this base.

It was no exaggeration to say that.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ07</ID>
    <Text>Lhasa Base is one of the bases of the Zeon Far East Army.


Commonly known as Apsaras base.


This is on the ground


It is one of the bases responsible for researching and developing new weapons.



A new type of mobile armor called Apsaras


Once completed, it is a long-awaited goal to create the Federation's general command headquarters.


It is also said that it is possible to attack Jaburo.



However, one mobile armor or MS,


However, the reality is that it is not easy enough to have an influence on the war situation.


In the current situation on the ground,


I want to believe in such things,


I guess it's unavoidable...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ08</ID>
    <Text>In late November, in Zeon's home country, Side 3,

In order to prepare for the Federation Forces' space invasion,

Its troops and supplies are used as the homeland defense line.

Granada on the Moon, Space Fortress Solomon,

Then, he made a move to focus on A Baoa Ku.



At this point, the ground forces

In effect, they were separated.



Left behind on an unfamiliar surface,

In a situation where even supplies could not be maintained,

The soldiers were becoming more and more exhausted day by day.




Meanwhile, as a beachhead with the universe

At California Base, which was barely functioning,

It has been reported that relief supplies will be dropped from space.

Even among the soldiers on the front lines,

That was a glimmer of hope.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ09</ID>
    <Text>By the end of November, Zeon is home.

On Side 3, in order to prepare for the Federation Forces' space invasion,

Its troops and supplies are used as the homeland defense line.

Granada on the Moon, Space Fortress Solomon,

Then, he made a move to focus on A Baoa Ku.


At this point, ground forces

In effect, they were separated.



Left behind on an unfamiliar surface,

In a situation where even supplies could not be maintained,

The soldiers were becoming more and more exhausted day by day.



Meanwhile, one of the resistance bases in the Far East

Lhasa Base was attacked by federal troops,

He was in crisis.


If this falls, the Far East will follow Europe.

It could have fallen into the hands of the Federation...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ10</ID>
    <Text>Led by Commander Char Aznable, also known as the Red Comet.

According to an investigation by Mad Angler Team,

Finally, the Federal Forces General Headquarters Jaburo

The exact location has been discovered.



And after receiving this,

By troops kept at California Base

An all-out attack was decided.



This battle will decide the fate of the Zeon ground control forces.

It was obvious….



If we win, the military balance on the ground will be

I lean towards Zeon again,

If we lose, we will lose most of our military reserves,

Before the Federation's mop-up operation,

He receives a blow so deep that he can't even resist...


This strategy could be called a gamble...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ11</ID>
    <Text>Our troops are in charge of


Achieving the first goal of destroying air defense equipment,


Finally, we entered the inside of Jaburo.







The inside of Jaburo is


Made using a limestone cave,


It was a vast underground cavern.




While being captivated by the mystery of nature,


A dark underground path like a complicated maze


We pushed forward for victory...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ12</ID>
    <Text>Zeon's strategy to capture Jaburo is

It ended with a crushing defeat for our army...



Most of the paratroopers were destroyed on the ground,

Although only a small number of troops succeeded in infiltrating the inside,

Those troops also

It was destroyed in the face of the Federation's MS unit...



The blocks we successfully sabotaged are:

After all, it is only a small part of Jaburo,

In the end, the effect is not enough to reduce the current momentum of the Federation.

There was not….



Due to the failure of this strategy,

The situation will become even worse in the future

In order to help friendly troops who may fall,

At this point, anyway...

Getting out alive was the top priority...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ13</ID>
    <Text>Due to the defeat in the battle to capture Jaburo, which was about to make a comeback,

California Base lost most of its strength.

The Zeon Ground Suppression Force is

There was no longer any way to oppose the Federation.


In response, the Federation has rebuilt its Starfleet.

The launch was a success, and finally,

He was showing his readiness for the final battle in space...


Well then, that's it

I wish you would leave me alone,

To be polite, there is no such thing as a Zeon mop-up operation.

Looks like it's being planned.


Well, if the other side is motivated,

This too, until the end, until we're together.


I…,

No, Brauer's team is

It's shocking how bad you are at giving up.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ14</ID>
    <Text>Due to the defeat in the battle to capture Jaburo, which was about to make a comeback,

California Base lost most of its strength.

The Zeon Ground Suppression Force is

There was no longer any way to oppose the Federation.


In response, the Federation has rebuilt its Starfleet.

The launch was a success, and finally,

He was showing his readiness for the final battle in space...


Well then, that's it

I wish you would leave me alone,

To be polite, there is no such thing as a Zeon mop-up operation.

Looks like it's being planned.


Well, if the other side is motivated,

This too, until the end, until we're together.


I…,

No, Brauer's team is

It's shocking how bad you are at giving up.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ15</ID>
    <Text>Lhasa Base is one of the bases of the Zeon Far East Army.

The base was surrounded by federal forces and fell.




However, it was being developed in secret at this base.

Due to the Apsaras' counterattack, the Federation's suppression forces also

It had been a devastating blow.


Currently, a federal investigation team and

Only a minimum number of garrison troops are stationed there.




According to the information I've gathered, underground of this base,

There is a separate block of underground storage.



...The contents are pretty predictable.



Maintaining an army costs money.

At all costs, before the Federation discovers this,

I want to steal it.</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ16</ID>
    <Text>California base.

This is the largest base of the Zeon Ground Suppression Force.



However, it is only a matter of time before it falls here as well.

Let's take it as me, the like-minded friends I've met

I don't want to lose it in a place like this.



When the Jaburo attack fails,

There is no longer any possibility of rebirth on earth.



To be honest, the sooner you decide on a hiding place,

Until the guys in space turn the tide of the war.

I think I should lay low.


There's no way our captain would hear something like that...




Well, if you're with them,

Even if I have to die here...Is this what I really want?</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ17</ID>
    <Text>On our way to Africa,


from troops stranded in the Desert.


Received a request for relief.


It would be easier if I could transport it with a gau,


Most of it was lost in Jaburo;


As expected from Klaus, it was impossible to arrange it.




I managed to arrange a gallop and overland.


We decided to support the evacuation.


However, this area is in the midst of a Zeon mopping up operation.


It was a route for federal troops...




It looks like it's going to be a tiring job for the first time in a while...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ18</ID>
    <Text>We owe it to Tord


From California Base on the verge of collapse,


I succeeded in escaping...




On the ground,


The African front barely continues to resist,


It could be said that it had completely fallen under the control of the Federation.






In order to connect our hope of escape to space,


Throw away the gau that is too conspicuous, under this situation,


To ensure safe movement of troops,


They decided to attack a Federation transport unit...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ19</ID>
    <Text>In mid-December, California Base and

The Federation's two major mop-up operations on the African front are

Each of them had reached their peak.

In the face of an overwhelming difference in strength, the Zeon ground forces...

It was on the verge of destruction.


However, in Africa, there are

Countless Zeon underground bases have been built,

Most of them have their entrances tightly closed,

For the time of counterattack that will come someday,

It was in a state of hibernation.

In this case, these bases, by their nature,

It becomes difficult not only to conquer, but also to discover.

The reality was that the Federation had no choice but to ignore it.


There is no longer even an opportunity for activity.

Our troops, who had lost their grip,

They had set up camp at a mining base and were hiding there...

It seems like it won't be easy until the very end...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ20</ID>
    <Text>In order to fulfill the desire to escape to space,

We are in the North Pole, where the Federation space base is located.

I was on my way.




Even if you could go into space, you would still be under the watchful eye of the Federation.

Escape and safely reach the moon or neutral side 6.

I don't know if I can escape...

Still, we are now

I had no choice but to hang on to that faint hope.





But in a corner of my heart,

Isn't there still something we can do on the ground?

...That thought remained.




Tord...I won't ask you to protect me.

Please at least watch over us...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_PROLOGUE_MZ21</ID>
    <Text>The calendar starts from Universal Century 0079.

It's the end of December, about to reach 0080.



It was supposed to end on a good note, but...



sorry,

Please hang out with me just a little longer.




The mining base where we are hiding is at this last minute.

discovered and landed by troops from the Indian Ocean,

I was completely surrounded...



Fortunately, I guess it's because of what I've done so far.

They will accept you if your escape is successful.

The base has been found.




Now, this really looks like it's going to be the last battle...</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ01_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Desert</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ02_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Near Odessa</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ03_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Near Odessa</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ04_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Belfast</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ05_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Snow field</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ06_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Seattle</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ07_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Valley, Area 526</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ08_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Valley</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ09_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Lhasa Base</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ10_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Jaburo, surface</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ11_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Jaburo, underground</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ12_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Jaburo, surface</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ13_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Valley</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ14_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Seattle</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ15_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Lhasa City</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ16_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>California Base</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ17_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Desert</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ18_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Snow field</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ19_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Africa Mining Base</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ20_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Arctic Base</Text>
  </Block>
  <Block>
    <ID>SPACE_MZ21_TEXT_01</ID>
    <Text>Africa Mining Base</Text>
  </Block>
</Texts>